python a high-level interpreted programming language famous for its
python 一种高级解释性编程语言，以其
zen-like code it's arguably the most popular language in the world because
类似 zen 的代码而闻名，它可以说是世界上最流行的语言，因为
it's easy to learn yet practical for serious projects in fact you're watching
它很容易学习，但对于严肃的项目来说很实用事实上你现在
this youtube video in a python web application right now it was created by
正在 python 网络应用程序中观看这个 youtube 视频 它由
guido van rossum and released in 1991 who named it after monty python's flying
guido van rossum 创建并于 1991 年发布，他以 monty python 的飞行马戏团命名它，
circus which is why you'll sometimes find spam and eggs instead of foo and
这就是为什么你有时会
bar in code samples it's commonly used to build server-side applications like
在代码示例中找到垃圾邮件和鸡蛋而不是 foo 和 bar 它通常用于构建服务器端应用程序，如
web apps with the django framework and is the language of choice for big data
Web 应用程序 使用 django 框架，并且是大数据
analysis and machine learning many students choose python to start learning
分析和机器学习的首选语言，许多学生选择 python 开始
to code because of its emphasis on readability as outlined by the zen of
学习编码，因为它强调可读性，正如 python 之禅所概述的那样，
python beautiful is better than ugly while explicit is better than implicit
漂亮胜于丑陋，而显式胜于隐式
python is very simple but avoids the temptation to sprinkle in magic that
python 非常简单，但避免了使用会导致歧义的魔法的诱惑，
causes ambiguity its code is often organized into notebooks where
它的代码通常被组织到笔记本中，其中
individual cells can be executed then documented in the same place we're
ind 可以执行单个单元格，然后在我们
currently at version 3 of the language and you can get started by creating a
当前处于该语言版本 3 的同一位置进行记录，您可以通过创建
file that ends in py or ipymb to create an interactive notebook create a
以 py 或 ipymb 结尾的文件来开始创建交互式笔记本
variable by setting a name equal to a value it's strongly typed which means
通过设置名称来创建变量等于它是强类型的值，这意味着
values won't change in unexpected ways but dynamic so type annotations are not
值不会以意外的方式更改，而是动态的，因此不需要类型注释
required the syntax is highly efficient allowing you to declare multiple
语法非常高效，允许您
variables on a single line and define tuples lists and dictionaries with a
在单行上声明多个变量并使用文字语法定义元组列表和字典
literal syntax semicolons are not required and if you use them and
分号是 不是必需的，如果你使用它们并且有
experience pythonista will say that your code is not pythonic instead of
经验，pythonista 会说你的代码不是 pythonic 而不是
semicolons python uses indentation to terminate or determine the scope of a
分号 python 使用缩进来终止或确定
line of code define a function with the def keyword then indent the next line
一行代码的范围 使用 def 关键字定义一个函数，然后通常将下一行
usually by four spaces to define the function body we might then add a for
缩进四 空格来定义函数体，然后我们可能会向它添加一个 for
loop to it and indent that by another four spaces this eliminates the need for
循环并缩进另外四个空格，这消除了对 cur 的需要
curly braces and semicolons found in many other languages python is a
ly 大括号和分号出现在许多其他语言中 python 是一种
multi-paradigm language we can apply functional programming patterns with
多范式语言，我们可以将函数式编程模式应用于
things like anonymous functions using lambda it also uses objects as an
使用 lambda 的匿名函数之类的东西它还使用对象
abstraction for data allowing you to implement object-oriented patterns with
作为数据的抽象，允许您使用类之类的东西来实现面向对象的模式
things like classes and inheritance it also has a huge ecosystem of third-party
和继承它还拥有一个庞大的第三方库生态系统，
libraries such as deep learning frameworks like tensorflow and wrappers
例如 tensorflow 之类的深度学习框架和
for many high performance low level packages like open computer vision which
许多高性能低级包的包装器，例如开放计算机视觉，
are most often installed with the pip package manager this has been the python
这些包通常与 pip包管理器一起安装，这一直是 python
programming language in 100 seconds hit the like button if you want to see more
编程语言 100秒内点击喜欢按钮，如果你想看更多这样的
short videos like this thanks for watching and i will see you in the next
短片谢谢收看，我会在下一个看到你
one